one of the things I would like to create
I don't know what this sounds like
something definitely other people figure
out with me but there's a course I think
it was at Harvard MIT one of those top
universities it was a course and
Happiness and what makes people happy
there's one of the most popular courses
there's also a documentary I believe
called happy but what makes people happy
and having a way to rate your actual
happiness for your own news not just for
everyone else's that's that's what we
decided to do having a way to rate your
own happiness but also improve it so if
you don't have enough connection you
don't have enough then creating ways to
to do that from where you're at based on
your personality so not that you need to
be a type-a and I go get them in an
extrovert like how do you create
community with some your space and what
you have and how do we help each other
and so a happiness of course and a
happiness app that helps you track and
actually improve your real tangible
happiness if Apple this is why is this
the hardest part can you track of them
without the list Apple number 83